

# Prasanna Tuladhar

Full - Stack Javascript Developer

3 years experience in developing web / mobile applications, a deep understanding of user behaviour and satisfaction, and software optimization. Recent MIS graduate with an in-depth understanding of computer technologies and software development, connecting management decision making for organizational growth.

+47 96708761

tuladharprasan@gmail.com

me@prasannat.com

www.linkedin.com/in/prasanna-tuladhar





### Professional Skills

- Javascript / Typescript
- HTML 5 & CSS 3
- React JS, React Native
- Node JS (Express)
- PHP (Laravel)
- Database (MySQL, MongoDB)
- UI / UX (Figma)
- Graphics (Photoshop, Illustrator)
- Academic experience on Project Management, Data analytics, Management Control, Consumer Behavior.
- Growth hacking mindset
- Time management, Analytical
- Planning & Decision making
- Leadership, Teamwork and collaboration

## Work Experience

- 1) Application Developer (Web / Mobile) @ I.Click Kathmandu, Nepal (March 2018 – November 2020)
- Developed Web and mobile (android / iOS) applications. 0 (Laravel and React Native).
- 0 Cooperated with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- 0 Developed project concepts and maintained optimal workflow.
- 0 Created new page designs for split tests and promotions.
- 0 Worked with testing teams to end tests and make winning variations live.
- 0 Optimized page structures for better performance.
- Web Development Internship @ Sherpa Technologies 2) Thahity, Kathmandu, Nepal (August 2017 – December 2017)
- Designed websites using HTML, CSS, Javascript (Bootstrap framework).
- 0 Implemented recommendations into the website.
- 0 Determined customer needs and improved UX in response.
- Debugged problems with minimal guidance.
- Non Relevant: Delivery Courier, Foodora AS 3) Waldermar Thranes gate, Oslo, Norway (March 2021 – Current)
- Use a mobile application to navigate, pick up and deliver.

### Education

1) Master's in Management Information Systems (MIS)

University of South-Eastern Norway

Hønefoss, Ringerike, Norway (August 2020 – June 2022)

Thesis: Growth Hacking to retain customers in Nepalese E-commerce companies

- 0 A qualitative research to find how e-commerce businesses perceive and practice growth hacking to retain their customers.
- Bachelor's of Science in Computer Science and 2) Tribhuvan University (Prime College) Kathmandu ,Nepal (2013 – 2017)

Final year project: Developed an E-commerce website.



- English (IELTS 6.5)
- Norsk (Beginner A1)
- Nepali
- Hindi
- Newari (Mother Tongue)



## Certificate

1) Web Development Course Student Project Nepal Computer Institute, Nepal October 2016 - March 2017

**≥** Affiliation

Union member @ Fellesforbundet 1) Lilletorget 1 0184, Oslo, Norway March 2021 - Current



## Leisure



Sports: Football



Hiking & Trekking, Travel



Music: Guitar



Photography



Nature, Wildlife